Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Afrika Bambaataa recordings
      Suberies contains vinyl discs in which Bambaataa was the artist or played an important role in the production of the recording(s).
      - Planet rock, 1982; SR-25200; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-25201. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # 2141 610; A-side Matrix # 198 2812156 1 380 POLYGRAM
        21 Records
        Paris, France
      - Planet rock, 1982; SR-25201; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-25200. Multiple copies.
      - Planet rock (the remixes) (disc one), 1998; SR-17614; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-17615; SR-17616. Triple album.
        Catalog # HAL 12798; A-side Matrix # HAL 12798-1-2
        The Perfect Beat Records
        New York, New York
      - Planet rock (the remixes) (disc two), 1998; SR-17615; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-17614; SR-17616. Triple album.
        Catalog # HAL 12798; A-side Matrix # HAL 12798-5-6
      - Planet rock (the remixes) (disc three), 1998; SR-17616; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-17614; SR-17615. Triple album.
        Catalog # HAL 12798; A-side Matrix # HAL 12798-9-10
      - Return to planet rock (the second coming), 1989; SR-17617; Afrika Bambaataa and the Soul Sonic Force; Jungle Brothers; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        Catalog # YRC-786-64LP; A-side Matrix # YRC-786-64LP-A
        York's Records
        Brooklyn, New York
      - Planet rock '96, 1996; SR-17618; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-17619. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # HCL 2293; A-side Matrix # HCL-2293 A
      - Planet rock '96, 1996; SR-17619; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-17618. Multiple copies.
      - Planet rock - the album, 1986; SR-17620; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        Promo
        Catalog # TBLP 1007; A-side Matrix # TBLP-1007-A
        Tommy Boy
      - Planet rock 2000 - the next millenium, 2000; SR-17621; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        Catalog # PRM-2339; A-side Matrix # PRM2339-A
        Planet Rock Music
        Bronx, New York
      - Planet rock the '98 remixes (part two), 1998; SR-17622; Afrika Bambaataa and the Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-17624. Different discs.DJ
        Catalog # 12 AWX 1R; A-side Matrix # 12 AWX 1 DJ A
        Afro Wax Records
        London, United Kingdom
      - Planet rock (the remixes) (disc one), 1998; SR-17624; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-17622. Different discs. No entry in discogs, used similar release
      - Rock the house twinpak EP (disc one), 1997; SR-17625; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-17626. Double album.Test pressing. No entry in discogs, used similar release
        Catalog # HAL 12778; A-side Matrix # HAL-12778-A
      - Rock the house twinpak EP (disc two), 1997; SR-17626; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-17625. Double album.Test pressing. Same as 17625 but no "twinpak ep" and with purple vinyl.
        Catalog # HAL 12778; A-side Matrix # HAL-12778-C
      - Rock the house (disc one), 1997; SR-20858; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20859. Double album. Same as 17625 but no "twinpak ep" and with purple vinyl.
      - Rock the house (disc two), 1997; SR-20859; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20858. Double album.
      - Push my planet; Planet rock rmx, 2003; SR-20860; Afrika Bambaataa; Benassi, Benny (Box 161)
        Catalog # AM 52189; A-side Matrix # AM 52189/A
      - Looking for the perfect beat, 1989; SR-20861; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20862. Multiple copies. Re-issue.
        Catalog # TB-831; A-side Matrix # TB-831-A-RE-VERS 1
      - Looking for the perfect beat, 1989; SR-20862; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20861. Multiple copies. Re-issue.
      - Looking for the perfect beat, 1983; SR-20863; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20864. Multiple copies.Promo
        Catalog # TB-831; A-side Matrix # TB-831-A
      - Looking for the perfect beat, 1983; SR-20864; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20863. Multiple copies.Promo
      - Rock the house (disc one), 1997; SR-20865; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20866. Double album.
      - Rock the house (disc two), 1997; SR-20866; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20865. Double album.
      - Rock the house (disc two), 1997; SR-20867; Afrika Bambaataa and the Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        Test pressing, colored vinyl
        Hot Productions
        Miami, Florida
      - Frantic situation, 1984; SR-20868; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force; Shango (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20869. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # TB 849; A-side Matrix # TB-849-A
      - Frantic situation, 1984; SR-20869; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force; Shango (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20868. Multiple copies.
      - Don't stop...planet rock (The remix EP, Part 1), 1992; SR-20870; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        Catalog # ZANG29T; A-side Matrix # ZANG-29(T) A1
        ZTT
        United Kingdom
      - Don't stop...planet rock (The remix EP, Part 2), 1992; SR-20871; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        Annotated.
        Catalog # ZANG29TX; A-side Matrix # ZANG-29(TX) A1
      - Don't stop...planet rock (The remix EP) (disc one), 1992; SR-20872; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20873. Double album.
        Catalog # TBEP1052; A-side Matrix # 1052-1-A-1-RE
      - Don't stop...planet rock (The remix EP) (disc two), 1992; SR-20873; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soulsonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20872. Double album.
        Catalog # TBEP1052; A-side Matrix # 1052-1-C-1-RE
      - Looking for the perfect beat (Brutal Bill remix), 1998; SR-20874; Afrika Bambaataa & Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        Catalog # TB 330; A-side Matrix # TB 330-REI-A
      - Planet rock, 1982; SR-20875; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force; Music Patrol (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20876. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # TB 823; A-side Matrix # TB-823-A
      - Planet rock, 1982; SR-20876; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force; Music Patrol (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20875. Multiple copies.
      - Planet rock, 1982; SR-20877; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force; Music Patrol (Box 161)
      - Planet rock, 1987; SR-21107; Afrika Bambaataa & the Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force; Music Patrol (Box 161)
        Re-issue
      - Zulu Nation throw down (volume #2), 1980; SR-20878; Bambaataa; Zulu Nation; Soul Sonic Force; Harlem Underground Band; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        Catalog # 12x33 - 9; A-side Matrix # 12x33-9A
        Paul Winley Records
      - The death mix throwdown, 1987; SR-20879; Afrika Bambaataa; Cosmic Force; Soul Sonic Force; Harlem Underground Band (Box 161)
        Catalog # BLATLP 2; A-side Matrix # BLAT LP-2-A
        Blatant
      - Zulu Break, 1984; SR-20880; Afrika Bambaataa and the Soul Sonic Force; Jonzun Crew; Planet Patrol; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        Catalog # 821 769-1; A-side Matrix # 198 8 217 691 1 POLYGRAM
      - Looking for the perfect beat, 1983; SR-20881; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20882. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # 0930.112; A-side Matrix # 0930 112 S 1 0704 815 S 1
        Metronome
        Hamburg, Germany
      - Looking for the perfect beat, 1983; SR-20882; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20881. Multiple copies.
      - Renegades of funk!, 1984; SR-20883; Afrika Bambaataa & Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20884. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # 817 888-1; A-side Matrix # 160 8 178 881 A POLYGRAM
        Polydor
      - Renegades of funk!, 1984; SR-20884; Afrika Bambaataa & Soul Sonic Force; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20883. Multiple copies.
      - Renegades of funk!, 1983; SR-20885; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20886. Multiple copies.Promo
        Catalog # TB 839-A; A-side Matrix # TB-839-A
      - Renegades of funk!, 1983; SR-20886; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20885. Multiple copies.Promo
      - Renegades of funk!, 1984; SR-20887; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        Catalog # TB-839-A; A-side Matrix # TB-839-A
      - Renegades of funk!, 1984; SR-25202; Afrika Bambaataa & Soulsonic Force (Box 161)
        Catalog # AFRX 1; A-side Matrix # AFRX1 A 2 420 W
      - Feeling irie, 1993; SR-20888; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        Catalog # DFC 142; A-side Matrix # DFC 142-A
        DFC
        Bologna, Italy
      - Funky heroes, 1992; SR-20889; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        Catalog # ACE016; A-side Matrix # ACE 016 A1
        Acetate Ltd
      - Coke DJ-culture, 2003; SR-20890; Woody; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        Catalog # COKA01; A-side Matrix # COCA 01
        Klub Berlin Music Productions
        Berlin, Germany
      - Got that vibe, 2004; SR-20891; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20892. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # TB-2452-0; A-side Matrix # TB-2452-0 A
      - Got that vibe, 2004; SR-20892; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20891. Multiple copies.
      - Electro funk mix-down, volume one (disc one), 2001; SR-20893; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20894. Double album.
        Catalog # PRLP 401; A-side Matrix # PRLP 401-A
        New York DJ Service
      - Electro funk mix-down, volume one (disc two), 2001; SR-20894; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20893. Double album.
        Catalog # PRLP 401; A-side Matrix # PRLP 401-C
      - Looking for the perfect beat 1980-1985 (disc one), 2001; SR-20895; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20896. Double album.
        Catalog # TB1457; A-side Matrix # TB-1457-A
      - Looking for the perfect beat 1980-1985 (disc two), 2001; SR-20896; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20895. Double album.
        Catalog # TB1457; A-side Matrix # TB-1457-C
      - Got to get up, 1998; SR-20897; Afrika Bambaataa; Carpe Diem (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20898. Different discs.Promo
        Catalog # TMULTY42P; A-side Matrix # 12 MULTY 42P A-1-1
        Multiply Records
      - Got to get up, 1998; SR-20898; Afrika Bambaataa; Carpe Diem (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20897. Different discs.Remix, promo
        Catalog # TMULTY42PX; A-side Matrix # 12 MULTY 42PX A-1-1
      - Got to get up, 1998; SR-20899; Afrika Bambaataa; Carpe Diem (Box 161)
        Catalog # MTR2071; A-side Matrix # MTR-2071-A
        Mantra Vibes
        Milan, Italy
      - If you technolectro, 2002; SR-20900; Sirius B; Afrika Bambaataa; Hardy Hard (Box 161)
        Catalog # 74321 92370 1; A-side Matrix # B258787 01 A1 MK
        Electric Kingdom
        Germany
      - Pupunanny (remix), 1994; SR-20901; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20902. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # DFC 215; A-side Matrix # DFC 2I5 A
      - Pupunanny (remix), 1994; SR-20902; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20901. Multiple copies.
      - Pupunanny, 1994; SR-20903; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        Catalog # DFC 197; A-side Matrix # DFC 197 A
      - Power boy power, 1991; SR-20904; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        Catalog # VNR-56241; A-side Matrix # VNR-1-56241-Z1
        EMI Records USA
        Hollywood, California
      - Power boy power; Save the world, 1992; SR-20905; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        Catalog # DFC 063; A-side Matrix # DFC 063 A
      - Feeling irie (remix), 1993; SR-20906; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20907. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # DFC 156; A-side Matrix # DFC 156 A
      - Feeling irie (remix), 1993; SR-20907; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 161)
        In same jacket as # SR-20906. Multiple copies.
      - Just get up and dance, 1991; SR-20908; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20909. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # DFC 037; A-side Matrix # DFC 037-SIDE A BAMBAATAA 24-01-91 FZ
      - Just get up and dance, 1991; SR-20909; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20908. Multiple copies.
      - Just get up and dance, 1990; SR-20910; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20911. Different discs.
        Catalog # ZYX 6491-12; A-side Matrix # ZYX 6491-12 A-1
        ZYX Records
      - Just get up and dance, 1991; SR-20911; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20910. Different discs.
        Catalog # SPX-133; A-side Matrix # SPX-133 A
        Spitfire Music
        Barcelona, Spain
      - Just get up and dance, 1991; SR-20912; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 162)
        Catalog # 12MT 100; A-side Matrix # 12MT 100 A-1-1-2
        EMI USA
      - Just get up and dance (remix), 1991; SR-20913; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20914. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # DFC 043; A-side Matrix # DFC 043-A SIDE
      - Just get up and dance (remix), 1991; SR-20914; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20913. Multiple copies.
      - Just get up and dance (DNA remix), 1991; SR-20915; Afrika Bambaataa; DNA (Box 162)
        Catalog # DFC 048; A-side Matrix # DFC 048 A
      - Just get up and dance (Techno remix), 1991; SR-20916; Afrika Bambaataa; De Point (Box 162)
        Catalog # DFC 060; A-side Matrix # DFC 060 A
      - Just get up and dance (remix), 1991; SR-20917; Afrika Bambaataa; DNA; De Point (Box 162)
        Catalog # 12 MTX 100; A-side Matrix # 12 MTX 100 A-1-1-1-
      - Just get up and dance (rmx), 1995; SR-20918; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 162)
        Catalog # ZYX 7940-12; A-side Matrix # ZYX 7940-12-A
      - Get up and dance | Da potion; Boogie down Bronx, 2003; SR-20919; Afrika Bambaataa; Man Parrish; Staten Island Warriors (Box 162)
        Catalog # 666SIX; A-side Matrix # 666 SIX A
        (Man Parrish?-check test pressings for Bam release)
      - Just get up and dance (remixes), 1991; SR-20920; Afrika Bambaataa; De Point; Gemolotto, Andrea (Box 162)
        Catalog # V-56225; A-side Matrix # V-1-56225-Z2
      - Sho nuff funky, 1988; SR-20921; Afrika Bambaataa; Jazzy Jay; Max Go-Go Kidd (Box 162)
        Catalog # EM BAM 2; A-side Matrix # EMBAM-2 A-1-1-
        EMI
      - Funk (this is Jungle Sky 6) (disc one), 1999; SR-20922; Afrika Bambaataa; DJ Soul Slinger (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20923. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # JSK 150; A-side Matrix # JSK-148A-1A
        Jungle Sky
      - Funk (this is Jungle Sky 6) (disc one), 1999; SR-20923; Afrika Bambaataa; DJ Soul Slinger (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20922. Multiple copies.
      - Unity, 1984; SR-20924; Afrika Bambaataa; Brown, James (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20925. Multiple copies.
        Catalog # TB 847 A; A-side Matrix # TB-847-A
      - Unity, 1984; SR-20925; Afrika Bambaataa; Brown, James (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20924. Multiple copies.
      - Hell below, 1992; SR-20926; Afrika Bambaataa; Adamski (Box 162)
        Catalog # DFC 076; A-side Matrix # DFC 076 BIS A
      - Mind control, 1997; SR-20927; Afrika Bambaataa; Nebula Funk (Box 162)
        Catalog # DFC 1307; A-side Matrix # DFC 1307 A
      - Mind control (The Danmass Remixes), 1997; SR-20928; Afrika Bambaataa; Nebula Funk; Danmass (Box 162)
        Catalog # SPEC 120; A-side Matrix # SPEC-120-A1
        Dust 2 Dust Records
      - Funky heroes, 1992; SR-20929; Afrika Bambaataa (Box 162)
        Catalog # DFC 099; A-side Matrix # DFC 099 A
      - Fire (remixes)(disc one), 1999; SR-20930; Afrika Bambaataa; DJ Soul Slinger; DJ Odyssey; GrandMixer DXT (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20931. Double album.Test pressing
        Catalog # JSK160; A-side Matrix # SIMON-THE EXCHANGE JSK 160A
      - Fire (remixes)(disc two), 1999; SR-20931; Afrika Bambaataa; DJ Soul Slinger; DJ Odyssey; GrandMixer DXT (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20930. Double album.Test pressing
        Catalog # JSK160; A-side Matrix # SIMON-THE EXCHANGE JSK 160C
      - Fire (remixes)(disc one), 1999; SR-20932; Afrika Bambaataa; DJ Soul Slinger; DJ Odyssey; GrandMixer DXT (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20933. Double album.
        Catalog # JSK 160; A-side Matrix # SIMON-THE EXCHANGE JSK 160A
      - Fire (remixes)(disc two), 1999; SR-20933; Afrika Bambaataa; DJ Soul Slinger; DJ Odyssey; GrandMixer DXT (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20932. Double album.
      - Metal, 2004; SR-20934; Afrika Bambaataa; Numan, Gary (Box 162)
        Catalog # TB-2453-0; A-side Matrix # TB-2453-0A
      - Dark matter moving at the speed of light (disc one), 2004; SR-20935; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and the Millennium of the Gods (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20936. Double album.
        Catalog # TB 1601-1; A-side Matrix # TB-1601-1 A-REI
      - Dark matter moving at the speed of light (disc two), 2004; SR-20936; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa and the Millennium of the Gods (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20935. Double album.
        Catalog # TB 1601-1; A-side Matrix # TB-1601-1 C-REI
      - Eastside (disc one), 2003; SR-20937; Afrika Bambaataa; Various artists (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20938; SR-20939. Triple album.
        Catalog # EVSLP49; A-side Matrix # EVSLP 49 A-1-1
        Obsessive
      - Eastside (disc two), 2003; SR-20938; Afrika Bambaataa; Various artists (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20937; SR-20939. Triple album.
        Catalog # EVSLP49; A-side Matrix # EVSLP 49 C-1-1
      - Eastside (disc three), 2003; SR-20939; Afrika Bambaataa; Various artists (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20937; SR-20938. Triple album.
        Catalog # EVSLP49; A-side Matrix # EVSLP 49 E-1-1
      - Jazzy sensation | Lessons 1-3, 1998; SR-20940; Afrika Bambaataa; Afrika Bambaataa & The Jazzy 5; Double Dee & Steinski (Box 162)
        In same jacket as # SR-20941. Different discs.